### Contact

+1-404-343-9453 (Mobile) msgmanu18@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/smanu1987 (LinkedIn) concept-inc.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Microsoft SQL Server ASP.NET Microsoft CRM

## Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Microsoft Certified: Dynamics 365 Field Service Functional Consultant Associate

Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 Customization & Configurations (MB2-866)

Microsoft Certified: Power Apps + Dynamics 365 Developer Associate

Microsoft Certified: Dynamics 365 Sales Functional Consultant Associate

Microsoft Certified: Dynamics 365 + Power Platform Solution Architect Expert

# Manu Sharma

Microsoft Certified Dynamics 36 & Power Platform Solution Architect, SME for Field Service/Project Operations

Houston

# Summary

A decade+ of experience implementing Microsoft Dynamics CRM based solutions. Expertise in Field Service, Project Service Automation and Mobility Solution.

Domains: High-Tech, Supply Chain, Distribution, Banking, Manufacturing, Oil & Gas, Real Estate & Brokerage, Government, Public Health

## Experience

Concept Software & Services Inc Solutions Architect January 2015 - Present (5 years 8 months) Alpharetta, Georgia

National Oilwell Varco Consultant - Dynamics 365 CE/FSM/PSA June 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 2 months) Houston, Texas

Ingram Micro
Consultant - Microsoft Dynamics 365
October 2018 - June 2019 (9 months)
Irvine, California

East West Bank
Consultant - Microsoft Dynamics CRM
June 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 5 months)
El Monte, California

Armando Montelongo Companies Consultant - Microsoft Dynamics CRM March 2015 - May 2017 (2 years 3 months) San Antonio, Texas

HCL Technologies Technical Consultant February 2013 - January 2015 (2 years)

Noida Area, India

Unique Identification Authority of India Technical Lead February 2013 - January 2015 (2 years) New Delhi Area, India

LineBeyond, Inc.
Technical Consultant
May 2012 - January 2013 (9 months)

Wipro Limited Software Engineer August 2010 - May 2012 (1 year 10 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Sopra Steria Student Intern June 2009 - July 2009 (2 months) Noida Area, India

# Education

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science and
Engineering · (2006 - 2010)